Teguh Prabowo Wijangkoro

Programmer

Semarang, Jawa Tengah ID

□ teguh.pw20@gmail.com □ +6281215541064

negadive in Teguh Prabowo Wijangkoro



Experienced Back End Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in SQL, PHP, C++, Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), and English. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Information System from Universitas Dian Nuswantoro.

SKILLS

Python Database Javascript

FastAPI Pandas MySql sqlite

WORK EXPERIENCE (3)

Backend Developer at PT Talenta Informasi Teknologi

Mar 2020 - Current



Design and implement server-side features and API using FastAPI framework

- Involve in database structure decision making
- Integrate third party service like Firebase, Midtrans

Assistant Lecturer at Dian Nuswantoro University

Jan 2018 - Jan 2019



Assisting lecturer in Database course

Assistant Lecturer at Dian Nuswantoro University

Jan 2017 - Jan 2018



Assisting lecturer in Programming and Algorithm course

PROJECTS (3)

Pemesanan Online Tiket Wisata

Jun 2020 - Aug 2020

PHP MySQL HTML CSS JavaScript

Prototype aplikasi pemesanan tiket wisata secara online

Integrasi Sederhana Telegram-bot dan Google Spreadsheet

Feb 2020 - Feb 2020

JavaScript

Integrasi sederhana mengirim pesan setiap pembuatan row baru pada Google Spreadsheet

Aplikasi Recency, Frequency, Monetary (RFM)

Mar 2019 - Mar 2019

PHP HTML CSS JavaScript

Prototype aplikasi analisa RFM otomatis

EDUCATION (2)

Bachelor Information System at Dian Nuswantoro University

2016 - Current

Highschool Mekatronika at SMK Negeri 1 Batam

2012 - 2015

LANGUAGES

English

Indonesia

Intermediate

Native speaker